ILGWU Political/Legislative Department, Evelyn Dubrow Papers 5780/142
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Calendar, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Meetings and Bills - Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Health Care, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Congress - General, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- A New Economic Initiative for the Former Soviet Republics, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Lists and Articles, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Vouchers in Finance Department, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Vouchers in Finance Department, 1990-1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- H.R. 5, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Congress - General, 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- ILWGU Campaign Committee, 1989-1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Campaign Committee Contributions, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Candidates for Congress, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- ILGWU State and Local Election, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Campaign Committee, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Thank You for Contributions Letters, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Federal Elections Commission, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Correspondence between Jay Mazur and Evelyn Dubrow, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Requests for Contributions, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Materials Received from ILGWU Campaign Committee (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Legislative Newsletters and Bulletins, 1976-1995 (Box 28, Folder 23)